{
  "Questions": {
    "Question1": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "0",
        "correctAnswer1",
        "1",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer1",
      "question": "question1"
    },
    "Question10": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "0",
        "1",
        "correctAnswer10",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer10",
      "question": "question10"
    },
    "Question11": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "correctAnswer11",
        "0",
        "1",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer11",
      "question": "question11"
    },
    "Question12": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "0",
        "1",
        "2",
        "correctAnswer12"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer12",
      "question": "question12"
    },
    "Question13": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "0",
        "correctAnswer13",
        "1",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer13",
      "question": "question13"
    },
    "Question14": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "0",
        "1",
        "correctAnswer14",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer14",
      "question": "question14"
    },
    "Question15": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "correctAnswer15",
        "0",
        "1",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer15",
      "question": "question15"
    },
    "Question2": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "0",
        "1",
        "2",
        "correctAnswer2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer2",
      "question": "question2"
    },
    "Question3": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "0",
        "correctAnswer3",
        "1",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer3",
      "question": "question3"
    },
    "Question4": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "correctAnswer4",
        "0",
        "1",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer4",
      "question": "question4"
    },
    "Question5": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "0",
        "1",
        "2",
        "correctAnswer5"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer5",
      "question": "question5"
    },
    "Question6": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "correctAnswer6",
        "0",
        "1",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer6",
      "question": "question6"
    },
    "Question7": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "0",
        "correctAnswer7",
        "1",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer7",
      "question": "question7"
    },
    "Question8": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "0",
        "1",
        "2",
        "correctAnswer8"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer8",
      "question": "question8"
    },
    "Question9": {
      "answerChoices": [
        "0",
        "correctAnswer9",
        "1",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "correctAnswer9",
      "question": "question9"
    }
  },
  "Rooms": {
    "FullRooms": {
      "-MzG8cfISYh__9n4QuqR": {
        "chosenAnswer": "correctAnswer7",
        "currentQuestion": "Question7",
        "index": 9,
        "player1": "9nNgD7fv3EUJX3rz1nPOB2JmTMo1",
        "player2": "Wy9J13ERhMRI6tclx2tItFPuTQg2",
        "questions": [
          "Question9",
          "Question10",
          "Question1",
          "Question4",
          "Question2",
          "Question3",
          "Question5",
          "Question8",
          "Question6",
          "Question7"
        ]
      }
    }
  },
  "Users": {
    "9nNgD7fv3EUJX3rz1nPOB2JmTMo1": {
      "currentRoom": "-MzG8cfISYh__9n4QuqR",
      "email": "leo@mail.com",
      "lose": 6,
      "point": 410,
      "username": "Leo",
      "win": 19
    },
    "Wy9J13ERhMRI6tclx2tItFPuTQg2": {
      "currentRoom": "-MzG8cfISYh__9n4QuqR",
      "email": "jack@mail.com",
      "lose": 13,
      "point": 350,
      "username": "Jack",
      "win": 15
    }
  }
}